export default questions = [
	{
		title: "Numbers",
		questions: [
			{
				points: 100,
				question: "How many different values can a boolean have?",
				answer: "2",
			},
			{
				points: 200,
				question:
					"What number is typically the index number of the first item in a code structure?",
				answer: "0",
			},
			{
				points: 300,
				question:
					"Referring to the type of bit computing in its processor, what number is in the name of Nintendo's first primarily 3-dimensional console?",
				answer: "64",
			},
			{
				points: 400,
				question:
					"As 1000 is not a power of 2, what number is typically used as the actual number of bytes in a kilobyte (or kibibyte)?",
				answer: "1024",
			},
			{ points: 500, question: "?", answer: "---" },
		],
	},
	{
		title: "Coding Concepts",
		questions: [
			{
				points: 100,
				question: "What kind of structure runs a piece of code multiple times?",
				answer: "Loop",
			},
			{ points: 200, question: "?", answer: "Object-Oriented Programming" },
			{
				points: 300,
				question:
					'What is the term for objects in a class getting attributes passed down from "parent" classes?',
				answer: "Inheritance",
			},
			{
				points: 400,
				question: "What is the process of running a function on itself?",
				answer: "Recursion",
			},
			{
				points: 500,
				question:
					'What is the term for objects in a class getting attributes passed down from "parent" classes?',
				answer: "Inheritance",
			},
		],
	},
	{
		title: "Animals",
		questions: [
			{
				points: 100,
				question:
					"Coined after a moth caused a computer malfunction, what term refers to unintentional software faults and also insect-like creatures?",
				answer: "Bug",
			},
			{
				points: 200,
				question:
					"What word for a scam that tries to lure out sensitive data sounds like a common aquatic creature?",
				answer: "Phish",
			},
			{
				points: 300,
				question:
					"What kind of malware with a name referring to a legless creature is characterized by rapid self-duplication affecting bandwidth?",
				answer: "Worm",
			},
			{
				points: 400,
				question:
					'What kind of bird is "Tux", the mascot for Linux operating systems?',
				answer: "Penguin",
			},
			{
				points: 500,
				question:
					"What network troubleshooting and packet analyzing software contains the name of an aquatic predator in its name?",
				answer: "Wireshark",
			},
		],
	},
	{
		title: "Electricity",
		questions: [
			{
				points: 100,
				question:
					"What do you call a material, such as a metal, that carries electrical current well?",
				answer: "Conductor",
			},
			{
				points: 200,
				question: "Which part of a circuit opposes the flow of electricity?",
				answer: "Resistor",
			},
			{
				points: 300,
				question:
					"What term refers to the difference in electrical potential in a circuit?",
				answer: "Voltage",
			},
			{
				points: 400,
				question:
					"Which kind of electrical current periodically reverses current direction and is typically represented by a sine wave?",
				answer: "Alternating Current (AC)",
			},
			{
				points: 500,
				question:
					"Which German physicist is the namesake for the unit for resistance and a formula relating resistance to current and voltage?",
				answer: "Georg Ohm",
			},
		],
	},
	{
		title: "Miscellaneous",
		questions: [
			{ points: 100, question: "?", answer: "" },
			{
				points: 200,
				question:
					"Digital images are displayed using usually thousands of what small square unit?",
				answer: "Pixel",
			},
			{ points: 300, question: "?", answer: "---" },
			{ points: 400, question: "?", answer: "" },
			{ points: 500, question: "?", answer: "---" },
		],
	},
];
